Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/zubinsethna-212247b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

College Recruiting
Technical Recruiting
Screening

zubin sethna

University Recruiter at Microsoft

Karnataka

Summary

With over 10+ years of experience in the field of Recruitment and 9 years specifically in University Relations, I am currently working as a University Recruiter. The roles held have spanned across B-Schools and Tech Colleges giving me in-depth knowledge in both.

I'm super thrilled to be back at Microsoft and being a part of the Dream Makers team:-)

Experience

Microsoft
University Recruiter
February 2019 - Present (1 year 7 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Intuit

University Recruiter
December 2013 - January 2019 (5 years 2 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

My experience entails:

- Creating vision and strategies for short and long term University Recruitment plans
- Strategizing and executing University Relations with faculty and students alike
- Building programs which helps grow the Brand Attribute for the company amongst the Early Career Talent
- Making the company presence felt and experienced in the campuses with focussed Engagement Initiatives
- End to end ownership of New Grad Hiring and Internship Program, have grown the hiring at India site from few dozens to hundred plus now

Google

Talent and Outreach Programs September 2012 - December 2013 (1 year 4 months)

Microsoft
College Recruiter
June 2010 - September 2012 (2 years 4 months)
Bangalore

Engaging and Hiring the Best Talent from the top B-Schools and Tech Schools in India.

Education

St Joseph's College of Business Administration, Bangalore PGDM, Human Resources & Marketing · (2008 - 2010)